[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Are you really, as a party, any nearer to knowing who will be the nominee?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I tend to think it'll be over before it goes to the convention but I can't prove that arithmetically.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Could this all be over by April or is it more likely, given what's been going on state by state so far, that this will run all the way to the convention?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "It's hard to say because every time you have one piece of conventional wisdom it's right for about a week and then wrong the next week, and flips back to being right again.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "From a betting point of view, where do you think this is all heading?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "I certainly hope it's not the Mormon thing.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Or is there something else going on?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, we have a government that seems to be, in effect, devouring its own people.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "But what is your sense about the apparent atrocity unfurling there?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Yes, I wish I could say that some of our followers, you know, produced the magic solution.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "What should America be doing?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Well, what we're seeing happen over Syria is really a kind of new alignment.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "What is the answer to how America should deal with their game?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Will journalists got to get into Syria, do you think?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, it's really hard to galvanize the international community to care about a crisis when you don't have a lot of footage coming in over television screens.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "What do you think about the situation involving the media there?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Well, I would say the thing to do is to keep us strong.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "It's not how do we fix this broken horror story, isn't it?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, let me say this.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "What do you think has gone wrong and what should he be doing now to fix it?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "What do you think is the biggest misconception about Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "You bet.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "And you believe he can bring that kind of business skill to America incorporated?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Let's discuss that after the break.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Created?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "I think it was quite good.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Was it fair?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "\"Good afternoon.\"", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Did he?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I mean Brangelina.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "You mean my daughter?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "OIGHT: Well, it's -- yes, it's a very unusual thing.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Is it weird to see how famous she's become?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Famously.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "It has been a rocky road, isn't it?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I did the best I could to try to give her advice.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "What's the most sensible advice that you as a former Oscar winner can give her?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Well, I think that -- I think I'm a better person.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Was that an unfair thing to infer?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "This is turning into a Piers Morgan --", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "What have you learned about yourself?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Well, it's not important.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Do you find it uncomfortable talking about yourself like that?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "I'm great, but I'm feeling a little uncomfortable because I was going to tell the same story that Jon Voight just told.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I do like to Tweet, my friend.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "You're quite an active little Tweeter, aren't you?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "It is addictive.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Do you find it's like taking over your life slightly?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "I think Obama.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Where is your money?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I find it fascinating, Piers, that you are having me on the show to really talk seriously about politics.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Do you think any of them, even if they do win the nomination race, could actually beat Barack Obama, especially if the economy goes on improving the way that it is?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Well, I'm -- yes, I am.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "You're a Democrat, right?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "I'm married to somebody who is not a Republican or a Democrat.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "You're married to a Democrat?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Well, he doesn't say.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "He's not a Democrat?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "I don't know, some lurid revelation that's going to --", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "What are you trying to get out of me?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Why did you -- I love this book.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Are you trying to get me divorced?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Well, two excellent questions.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "And why did you go for this cover?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Didn't you once get into a bathing suit with Henry Kissinger?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I was at a party.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "Who sets you up on this?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Only for television I do that.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "Probably a tendency to get on desks and come raging towards you like a hungry hyena?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "Well, I am.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "What's that all about?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "It's how I say hello.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "How does Chelsea know?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "Well, I was hoping you would ask me.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Would you mind if we do this in the studio next time, then?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "Because it will make you laugh.", "docId": "120208pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Tell me one good reason why people should buy this book?", "qSentId": 676}]